matthew frost

http://www.matthewfrost.com/ https://github.com/Exupery

summary

Currently the Software Engineer at StopBadware, where I design, build, and maintain the applications and databases that drive StopBadware's mission of making the Web safer through the prevention, mitigation, and remediation of badware websites. It is incredibly exciting and rewarding to do my small part in improving Web safety for everyone.

In early 2012 I completed my Bachelor's of Science in Information
Technology - Software from Western Governors University after several years
of Food & Beverage management. I originally began learning to program only
to assist in my hobby of stock trading with no intention of a career change,
but soon it was clear I was enjoying the coding not because it would lead to
better trading, but because I was truly enjoying programming. It was then I
decided my future lay not with hotels, but with software development.
Specialties: Web-applications, object-oriented programming, database
utilization, code optimization, agile development

skills

Java

- Ruby on Rails
- Scala
- JavaScript
- C++
- Perl

• Lua

- MySQL
- MongoDB
- PHP
- jQuery
- Databases
- Web Applications
- Redis

experience

StopBadware

02 / 2012 - Present

Software Engineer

Designs, builds, and maintains the applications and databases that drive StopBadware's work in making the Web safer through the prevention, mitigation, and remediation of badware websites. I'm a strong believer in using the right tool for the job so we have a varied stack that reflects that; we use a mix of Java, Ruby on Rails, and PHP together with MySQL and MongoDB.

Boston Technologies Inc

08 / 2010 - 02 / 2012

Team Manager - Trading Systems Analytics

Managed a team providing support to an international clientele for a wide range of technical and financial issues

education

Western Governors University

2010 - 2012

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) , Software Development